-------------Another 2D Platformer Manual----------------------
Controls:
You can navigate across the main menu with the arrow keys
 (up and down) and with the "W" and "S" keys.
In the options menu, you can enable/disable the music and
the sounds of the game. To choose an option, you can click
the desired button to enable-disable that option.

Start the game:
Once you start the game, you will find the first level, and
you goal is to reach the portal to the next level.

The control on the game are:
Left arrow key (<-): the character goes to the left.
Right arrow key(->): the character goes to the right.
Down arrow key(↓): the character slide down to the platforms.
Space bar(␣): the character will jump. You can press the 
space bar twice to do a double-jump.

Power-ups:
There are two main power-ups on the game:

Life+1: A heart that increases one life to your counter. 
There is a limitation: you can't have more than 3 lives, if
you get your third life, you will get 1000 points every time
you get a life+1 power-up.

Extra jump: A ball that makes you jump higher for 5 seconds.
You can reach places you can't do normally without the power-up.

There are other abilities that you will found during your gameplay.